keycaptcha.com 2012-05-11

# KeyCAPTCHA - KeyCAPTCHA Privacy Policy

All personal information is stored in the KeyCAPTCHA’s servers located in the European Union, the Swiss Confederation, and the United States of America. 

### 1\. Definitions

**Cookie** is a small amount of data created by a web service or webpage and stored on the user’s computer in a file that permanently allows a web server to identify a user and serve up customized web pages and/or login information to the user's web browser when revisiting a web page. 

The website’s visitor can modify his or her browser setting to decline cookies. There are various ways to perform this setting in different web browsers. To find out how to perform it in your browser, read your browser's manual. 

### 2\. Information stored by KeyCAPTCHA Service

KeyCAPTCHA Service does not store any personal information of the Service’s users except information requested when the user signs up to KeyCAPTCHA at www.keycaptcha.com and information required to integrate KeyCAPTCHA Service with the user’s website. 

KeyCAPTCHA Service collects anonymous information through the cookie technology on the websites using the KeyCAPTCHA Service. This information is not private and by no means can identify any individual or legal entity. 

### 3\. Use of Information received from the KeyCAPTCHA Service’s Users

Personal information received by the KeyCAPTCHA Service can exclusively be used to contact the KeyCAPTCHA Service’s users and to provide a proper functioning of KeyCAPTCHA Service. 

### 4\. Change of Your Contact Data

You are able to change your contact data at any time if you go to the “My profile” page available to any user logged into the KeyCAPTCHA website using his or her account. 

### 5\. Changes in Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy through publishing a revised Privacy Policy at the KeyCAPTCHA website. Periodically you shall visit the page to make sure that you are familiar with and agree to all changes. 

This Privacy Policy is exclusively related to the KeyCAPTCHA webite and Service and by no means governs any other aspects of the users’ working and security on the Internet.
